articleinsider.com 2010-02-02

# Privacy Policy | Article Insider

What Does Our Privacy Policy Cover?

Our policy covers how ArticleInsider handles personal information that ArticleInsider collects and receives at the sites at which this policy is posted, including information related to your past use of ArticleInsider products and services.

This policy does not cover how ArticleInsider treats personal information that it gets from other sources, such as offline, on other websites, or via email communications. Also, our policy does not apply to the activities of companies that ArticleInsider does not own or control, or to people that ArticleInsider does not employ or manage.

Collection and Use of Information

ArticleInsider collects personal information when you register and complete your user profile with ArticleInsider. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number.

When you register we request information including your name and email. Once you register with ArticleInsider and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

To help ArticleInsider display more relevant and targeted content and advertising we may also request demographic information such as age, gender, location and income level, however, providing this information to us is optional.

ArticleInsider automatically receives and stores information on our server and its logs collected from your browser, including your IP address, ArticleInsider cookie information (if any), and your page request(s).

ArticleInsider may use information for the following general purposes: to fulfill any of your requests for products and services, to customize the content and advertising we display for you, to improve our services, to contact you, conduct research, and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Children

Be aware that this website is designed for adult users, and ArticleInsider does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13, nor does it encourage or knowingly allow children under age 13 to register for an account.

If you are a parent and suspect that your child has given ArticleInsider with personally identifiable information, please contact us right away at [help@ArticleInsider.com](mailto:help@ArticleInsider.com).

Sharing and Disclosure of Information

ArticleInsider is not in the business of renting or selling personal information you give on this site with other people or nonaffiliated companies. ArticleInsider does, however, share your information to provide products or services you have requested, when you have given us your permission, and under the following circumstances:

We do provide that information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with ArticleInsider under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help ArticleInsider communicate to you offers from ArticleInsider and our marketing partners. These companies do not, however, have an independent right to share this information.

We also may share names and emails of members who join ArticleInsider as part of a co-branded partnership with ArticleInsider and any specific partner(s).

We may share general aggregate demographic information with third parties such as the media, advertisers, and government agencies. This general aggregate information is usually in the form of statistics, such as numbers of ArticleInsider users in a particular age group. Such general aggregate information is not traceable back to you as an individual.

We may share your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process or to otherwise cooperate with law enforcement agencies or officials, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

Be aware that we may share your information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ArticleInsider's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We will transfer information about you if ArticleInsider is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, ArticleInsider will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Cookies

ArticleInsider sets and accesses cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small bit of information used by the site to track your session. It does not contain any sensitive information. Generally speaking, no other web sites can access cookies set by ArticleInsider, nor can the ArticleInsider sites access cookies set by other web sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/ "http://www.networkadvertising.org").

Your Account Information and Communications

You are free to edit your ArticleInsider Account Information at any time by logging in to the site and entering the My ArticleInsider area.

You may also opt out of receiving ArticleInsider emails by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link. Please understand that even if you do opt out of receiving marketing materials, we reserve the right, and will continue to send you certain infrequent communications relating to the ArticleInsider service and/or your account, such as service announcements and administrative messages, which we consider to be part of your ArticleInsider account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

Confidentiality and Security

We do limit access to your personal information about you to those employees who we believe reasonably need to know that information to provide products or services to you or so that theycan do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

Your ArticleInsider Account Information is password-protected.

In certain areas ArticleInsider uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

Data you provide to us will be stored on our servers located either in our offices in California, or elsewhere in the United States or abroad. By providing us with your information, you understand and consent to the international transfer of your data.

You should take steps to protect yourself as well. For example:

Be certain not to share your password with anyone else, and take appropriate measures to prevent it from any unauthorized access or disclosure.

To learn more about how to protect yourself online, you may want to visit the U.S. government website [www.onguardonline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/ "www.onguardonline.gov").

Third Party Ads and Links

We allow third party advertisers to post advertisements on our site. These third parties may place cookies on certain pages of our site. We do not control those third parties, or their cookies. Our privacy policy does not cover those third party advertisers’ use of cookies.

The advertising ArticleInsider displays may be targeted to users of certain particular services and content. For example, if you view or click on a targeted ad, the advertiser (or other companies affiliated with the advertiser) may assume that you meet the targeting criteria — such as, men aged 30-40.

We may post links to other websites as a service to you. These sites are generally operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those websites and third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of thosewebsites and third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.

Our Privacy Policy is subject to change

This policy is effective as of December 1, 2008, 2008. ArticleInsider may update this policy from time to time. We will attempt to notify you about significant changes in the way we handle personal information by sending a notice to your primary email address set forth in your ArticleInsider account or by the prominent display of a notice on our website.

Questions?

To contact ArticleInsider for more information about this privacy policy or how your information is treated, please contact us by email at [help@articleinsider.com](mailto:help@articleinsider.com).

Copyright © 2003-2008 ArticleInsider, Inc. All rights reserved.
